Should I take your order?
Yes, miss. I'll order you a quinoa salad, please.
Of course. For the gentleman?
-Me an ass, please. -Why not?
-Excuse me. -Thank you.
-What was that, Felipe? -What was what?
Since when do you eat ass?
I don't know. I mean, I woke up and like I said:
"Ah, well, now a little ass."
Of course, right? Out of nowhere, you thought, "I'm going to get my ass handed to me today."
-Incredible, really. -What's the problem?
In the house you never want to eat ass. And suddenly we go out
and you get an uncontrollable desire to eat ass, right?
Well it's normal,
Anyone can get a craving for an ass one day.
Let's see, do you know if that ass had a decent life?
-No. -If it's free-range?
-No. -Was it a happy ass?
-No. -Then.
What if that ass has hemorrhoids, love?
We don't know what kind of ass it is.
A butt with hemorrhoids is very common.
Especially here in Mexico,
that the gastronomy has so much spice and all that.
Also, they're very careful with asses here.
Treat hemorrhoids with Nikzon.
It's a soft, pink ass...
I even went into the kitchen once and they had everything sanitized.
-All right, then. Miss. -Yes.
-I'll order you a mineral water. -Of course.
Listen, and now bring me my ass,
Please bring me lots of napkins,
because then I get very dirty.
Like when you eat wings, ribs...
-Of course. -Thank you.
Oh, love, if only I had known you liked asses so much,
we would have gone to the "culería" across the street
that have just opened in Roma.
-It's a more welcoming place, love. -I know, but it's kind of hipster.
I mean, I like the homemade ass better.
It's like it's juicier here, more pink, like... I don't know.
Go, go. Do you smell?
You see, just by smelling it, you know when an ass is good.
Yeah.
-You know what? I'm already craving one. -Yes? Order it.
Because then you just order the salad and you're left hungry.
Yes, that's right, you're right. Miss, excuse me.
Yes, tell me.
Look, I'm going to cancel what I ordered and I'm going to order the same thing as him.
Unfortunately it's not possible, he asked for the last ass of the day.
-What do you think? -Yes.
Don't you have a little one left over there?
It's all over. As is the house specialty,
-They ask for it a lot. -Of course.
Okay. Maybe we can share it if there's enough, right?
It depends on how hungry they are.
You know what? I'm really in the mood for some ass right now.
You know what? Don't worry. I'll order my quinoa salad.
-Of course. -No. Are you sure, my love?
-Yes, love, now. You pour it. -Yes. Listen,
Bring it to me right now, can you bring me a lot of lemons?
-Lemons for your ass? -Yes, thanks.
No, sir, don't do that.
Don Gonzalo has been here for more than 30 years
raising asses on a farm near Oaxaca.
My father was the first ass farmer in the region.
He was an excellent culiculturist. And, well, at first,
We only raised them here for our consumption,
But people really liked them, and we started selling them.
New people have already come here with their knowledge,
with his experience,
and they brought Nikzon, which treats hemorrhoids
and makes us have a better quality ass
and that we can export worldwide.
Don Gonzalo, his wife, Mariela, and his son, Juan,
They take care of the 7,000 hectare land daily.
From here as far as the eye can see,
you can see the ass breeding ground.
Yes, we have all kinds of asses.
There's a lot of variety. We have the angriest ones,
we have the most domesticated,
We already have a big butt, but... Bigger, but...
I mean, that one is harder to deal with,
because as they are soft, they are soft...
In fact, the other day we had to sacrifice one,
because its main fold had... It had been lost.
But well, it's the cycle of life.
The good thing is that you turn around and see that a new ass is already growing.
And that's very exciting, isn't it?
There is no money that can pay for those emotions.